Today I am 20 years old. I am zero
In AI. after listening to this podcast
Whatever I am doing now I have funds.
Step by step through the five levels. Level Zero
Here is Explore all the tools to understand
The Possibilities of What Can AI Do Today?
In this level one you should understand that friend
How does AI work? how does it give you
Text? Understand all that. After understanding that, you
Also understand that friend how can we talk to him
Do it? how do you do prompting. the level
Three here you go beyond text. Where
You will learn how images work?
How do videos work? Audio How To
Do you work? Level four. you learn how to
Build Products Using AI Right Now. Today
Our guest is Vaibhav Siccinty Rose School
Founder of. Vaibhav is every one of his business
Integrating AI into Aspect
Are. Today we will learn from them how to get AI Jobs
And which such AI is replacing it
There are tools that can help you make a lot of money
Can be done. Ideas that anyone can start today
Can do it as a solopreneur. you can
Build a Pipe Coders Who Are Very Good With
Talking with AI. Who can build personal AI
Solutions that only you will use. 2 Lakh, 3
Whoever charges lakhs will make it for you
I will give it. how much time will it take me b5
hours.
what
do
you
think
is
the
skill
that
today
hours.
what
do
you
think
is
the
skill
that
today
hours.
what
do
you
think
is
the
skill
that
today
It will make the people win in the times of. I think
everybody has to become something called an a
Generalist. who can solve any problem
Using AI. This specialist's worm
didn't you have to become a specialist at
Something. that is no more a vice thing to do
Any more.  Isn't it
scary? Jobs will come
Many more. Those Jobs That Refactoring Does
there were jobs, which were templated jobs, which
They were not original thinkers, their job was this
He will eat it. Three Tools That a Small Business Can Use
Owner should use it and run his business
Expand.
Before proceeding further please subscribe to this channel
Do it so that we can do more for you in this way
Keep making insightful and better podcasts.
And the audio experience of this entire show
Available on Spotify. where you find us
You can follow. Enjoy the show.
The way the world is moving ahead.
Now what will happen in the future? like what if
I am a job, today I am a person 20
Year old. I do a job. I am an AI
How do I proceed with help? So
This is the problem.
First of all I first of all
How is placement? I just got out of college
Am. How to get me placed through AI
Will
it
hurt?
How
to
do
placements
through
AI
Will
it
hurt?
How
to
do
placements
through
AI
Will
it
hurt?
How
to
do
placements
through
AI
Will it hurt? hmm
look friend what
tool are you using
Will it hurt? hmm
look friend what
tool are you using
Will it hurt? hmm
look friend what
tool are you using
I can make my placement easier for people
It will seem
better and quicker when
People with
placements
mean yaar da
People with
placements
mean yaar da
People with
placements
mean yaar da
The market is
horrible right now placements
No
brother,
see,
now
1.5
million
in
a
year
No
brother,
see,
now
1.5
million
in
a
year
No
brother,
see,
now
1.5
million
in
a
year
Kids do
engineering, we
do it for them
Kids do
engineering, we
do it for them
Kids do
engineering, we
do it for them
Placement rate
was normally 10%, we
are still at that
Placement rate
was normally 10%, we
are still at that
Placement rate
was normally 10%, we
are still at that
It has fallen to 6%
ok
so
the
number
of
jobs
in
the
market
for
ok
so
the
number
of
jobs
in
the
market
for
ok
so
the
number
of
jobs
in
the
market
for
Young people and middle level people are going to
diminish to a large extent and that is
It has just started. Right? so that's enough
It is difficult to get a job right now. it's not
About tools, my friend, it's okay to use tools
Is. Yours will probably increase a little more. But
The market is very dirty. And the reason I will
tell you. There is a recession going on. on top
Of that lot of companies are not hiring
Because they don't know what is going to happen.
Let's take IT. there is it
which hires the highest number of people in the
Country.
Ok?
Correct?
sector
Country.
Ok?
Correct?
sector
Country.
Ok?
Correct?
sector
what does he do? Outsource to outside companies
Let's work to make software.
Yes.
And
they
write
software
code.
Or
Yes.
And
they
write
software
code.
Or
Yes.
And
they
write
software
code.
Or
100s of thousands of people write code. Now
AI agents have become like cursors
Wind surf lovable bolts that can write
Code at a quality of a much better mid level
Engineer at 100 times the pace already
The IT industry which had made its own in India
US and First World Countries Needed
People who can write a lot
of code at a cheaper price
Price
at
a
cheaper
price
because
there
Price
at
a
cheaper
price
because
there
Price
at
a
cheaper
price
because
there
People are very expansive. GD Paper Capita
is so high that you can hire people at that
Scale.
As
a
result,
all
this
gets
outsourced
Scale.
As
a
result,
all
this
gets
outsourced
Scale.
As
a
result,
all
this
gets
outsourced
It was to
India.  The code we
have right now is
It was to
India.  The code we
have right now is
It was to
India.  The code we
have right now is
There is a need to outsource humans
Not there.
Because
AI can write
Not there.
Because
AI can write
Not there.
Because
AI can write
Most of the code already. I am not
Quoting this by the way. Entropic's Joe
The CEO said by end of this year 90%
Of the code will be written by AI. and very
Soon almost all the codes will be written by
AI.
The Future Programming Language for That
what will be the matter do you think what is
The Future Programming Language English
But what is a future programming
Language English is how we communicate
with the system what could that be the way we
Communicate with what the system is going to be
english in form of prompt
engineering you can call it the human
programming language but the real one
The Programming Language That's Going to Be
In the back end is going to be something that we
Humans won't understand
When we write code, sometimes the code
You must have seen how it looks. there are
hashtags there are stars right there are
Things Like Hash Include SDRH Right
it's a library call function these include
why is the word 'karke' used so every time
they are a new programming language that
is it created it is created in a way that
It is very easy for those who will write human code.
So that he can remember it. that is why
Pythons Went Very Popular. that's why all the
JavaScript Frameworks Went Very
It is very easy to write popular because
Comparatively than assembly language code when
If AI writes AI then it is not English brother
understands AI doesn't care if it is
alphabets characters words tu ai ko
will say write me the
most efficient code and
Write Me the Code in the Fastest Way Possible
so it will create its own programming
The Language Which You and I Cannot Say
Understand, I will send you a video
who are there two ai agents talking to each other
otherwise they realise that both of them are
Agents. and they talk in a language that
Humans can't understand. Which is called.
Yes. Gibnett. Gibernate and Something Like That.
Obviously that language was created by
Humans. For better communication. but it's a
The language that humans don't understand?
Outright. AI can create a language like
That and will create a language like that.
And I will show you the example. Entropic I
I explained it to you. AI that understands language
He does not understand humans. They
There is no English. so in programming too
That will happen. so an engineer today who us
I used to sit, all the managers used to sit in the US
Those people used to outsource his work
Hum
and
Yahan
Se
You
Used
Yahan
Se
You
Used
Yahan
Se
You
Used
people at very
low cost to
write code or that
people at very
low cost to
write code or that
people at very
low cost to
write code or that
will be agent why do we need humans
Give the person sitting there Rs 250
he is trying to manage 20 people only will manage 20
Agents: ok not everyone will lose their job but I will too
you need 10 people because these companies are also
EdI
So that's the coding
scene. Ok?  any job
It will not be
relevant.  I mean they will be
Relevant Jobs. So I think it comes
The role of Think Software Engineering
I hope I'm wrong. Whenever I say this I
hope i'm wrong because i don't want all
These things to
happen.  I think so
The job of software engineering is that
Will evolve into something like a scientist.
What do scientists do? doing research
Are.
We
are
the
only
software
Are.
We
are
the
only
software
Are.
We
are
the
only
software
Engineers that will exist who research in
Labs like Open AI and all that and big
Many more companies will come
Research companies will come where they can sit and do research
do. How a Human and an AI Agent Works
Can communicate better. most of the people who
Are writing code going to evolve in the new year
Rolls. I mean there is a someone's own I
Think Gartner has a report that says
50% of the engineers by 2028
Will not basically have to upskill
significantly to continue to have a job
of existing engineers. mark zagerberg
Said brother in meta, mid level
Engineers will not exist as they are
In a few years. all of that work will be
Done by AI. Only Senior Level Engineers
will exist which will be managed by AI
To the agents. so it's a crazy world that
We are getting in. so the guys who will
Continue to have jobs as software
Engineers. I don't know if jobs will come
That will happen but next three to four years are
Going to be a masseur according to me. Till New
Rolls Havelock. These are the top level people
that I feel will become something like a
The Software Scientist Who Will Invent
Things with the research companies. Rest of the
People will just communicate with an eye
Using painting. and this is very widely
Spoken. I am not making this up myself.
But friend, this is happening in my team too.
15 people had engineering subject, only five
People have a team and we are shipping more than that
Ever
what is everybody doing using cursor
Are you a Product Manager who wants to build an MVP?
Will not go to software engineer
My business team wants to make someone an MVP
It is their SOP to try some new feature
Build it yourself, bring the data and then the software
go to the engineer
product manager who you know the role of
product manager right i feel they are the
Guys Who Don't Thrive Like Anything Else
Because they have solid business sense.
I know what to make. and these two
Things happen to make a product.
Brother, the product manager is in my office
Codeship is doing it right
now.  because write the same
He gives it and hey, we
have to do the props. you have
To give a PRD. you have to explain
what you want. you have to give contact
Why a Product Manager Does It Very Well
Already. If it's a good product manager.
Dena thrives
crazily.  that too is a twig
will have to do it because that too one sheet first
The version will give you chatty. I mean yes that
is also there. But that's where the insides come from.
That's where the insides come from. so i feel
When it comes to jobs this is my belief
that the top 10% tier who were existing
Good who were not doing templated work.
hmm
will
do
very
well
because
original
hmm
will
do
very
well
because
original
hmm
will
do
very
well
because
original
Thinking is still needed. Because AI is so
He can only think as much as he is fed
Is. First take for example graphic designer
Take. if you like any design
You can create that AI. if you can think of
A dis AI can make it. if you can see an if
you saw a thing and you like that
AI can make it. If I See Your Thumbnails
I can make all thumbnails. you don't need a
Thumbnail Any More. Right? and i'm sure you
Are you using AI already there? Right? So two
jobs that were refactoring jobs, which
These were templated jobs, friend, I had some such
If I want to make it, I will make it. Joe Original
He was not a thinker, he would take away everyone's jobs.
original thinkers who are able to come
up with new thing which always made you wow
Those guys will make insane money because you don't
have to pay so many people any more now
If the graphic designer is leaving
The manager came and asked, brother graphic designer
Hire me what is coming out I said why
You should have four creative strategies
You can make a brief to the graphic designer
Brother please send
me such creative things
give you this
brief, give it to A
like or make sense i was not sure but i
still wanted to ask
Developers I Told You Coding Agents
helps them like crazy bhai presales
It was my team, you know we have done it
Course together right that's a presales team
If a lead comes, someone picks up the phone and tells him
calls knows who is this person
really
serious oh no we
have it for me
really
serious oh no we
have it for me
really
serious oh no we
have it for me
There was a team of 40 people, now all of that is done
Buy AI, AI calls you, you know sales then
Tere ko hack
paata hai the
amount of time we
Tere ko hack
paata hai the
amount of time we
Tere ko hack
paata hai the
amount of time we
lesser sir the amount of time you take to get
In touch with the lead, the higher is the chance of
Conversion. a human, can a human call in
3 minutes, every single time, you need a
Massive army for that. R Lead to Connection
Time used to be about 45 minutes to
Hours. Based on the day as much lead as came based
On that. Right now, it's exactly 10
Minutes. Why?
AI.  The AI ​​
lead comes in. Lead
Minutes. Why?
AI.  The AI ​​
lead comes in. Lead
Minutes. Why?
AI.  The AI ​​
lead comes in. Lead
The data is visible from AI. we expand that
into a script automatically in the back end
the call goes to who is a voice agent which
Sounds like a human. He asks on the call
hey raj this is jerry our internal ai
Agent name is Jerry. a jerry i am calling
From the Growth School Team. i saw that you
Have applied for this program. wanted to
Get a few more details about you.
whatever you say it captures all that
information and feeds that into our
CRM. CRM me major hota hai is this
Lead good or not? If the lead is good than a
Human Gets in Touch. so you are
Significantly Able to Scale the Business
While not scaling the team.
Post session we first posted on WhatsApp
Humans used to message. How was the feedback?
You must remember it. we used to send
Everyone because we want feedback? Now Our AI
Agent Which Is Again Jerry Riches Out To
People's rule. We saw you attended the session. You
Dropped off after 50 minutes, but I hope you
found value? is there any feedback you have
For us. it will talk to you like a human and
V Outright Savior A.I. We don't like it. We
And people are actually happy men. People R
Finding it fascinating. this second thing
also that we because we also teach AI
Are. so they feel that ok these guys know there
[ __ ]. But you get the point, right? in this
Level of Customer Support You Know What You Can
Happens. Everything is sort of it. Sales
Marketing
every prediction everything my marketing
Team is Shrinking Outreach SDR All the
SDR Outreach Is Automated With Agents
Firms
you know you can literally create a process
Today It Will Cost You $100 a Month May Be
every time there is a company you can put a
Logic like this is fine whenever a company more
The company raises $1 million in funding
I want the name of the sheet in Google Sheet
AI will keep looking for news all over the
World. every time a company has raises 10
Million dollars. it will find the company name
and whatever basic details on a google
Sheet. Then an agents form kicks in.
Do you know what is Agents Form?
imagine a bunch of employees lets say there
Everyday 10
leads are coming
like this.  We Let's
Everyday 10
leads are coming
like this.  We Let's
Everyday 10
leads are coming
like this.  We Let's
Getting 10000 leads from For Whatever
Reason. Right? If a human is given one
It takes a lot of time to get inside. Doing Research
yes, what is the name of the company? in Linden
I have to go and find it. Who is its founder? His
What is the email ID? An email for him
It has to be written. You can deploy 100 and 200
And 500 agents at once. which are parallel one by one
Complete research sheet about the company
He will fill it up. He got the name of the company. One
Found the link. by contacting him
Who is the founder? Who is the marketing head?
What is his email id? She told him last
What was written about whom in three posts
Is? based on all this infection will craft
An email and keep it ready. Now an AI
SDR Agent Comes Into The Picture The Moment
it has full information that and a sheet of data
saying this infection finish one
AI SDRs that are humans cold email
It will start typing automatically
He will follow up and reply if he gets a reply
he will also do it because you have told it how you
want to handle reply somebody says or i am
Open to explore but my budget is $100 and
would like sorry not right now we started
this dollar we can talk later but if he says
something close to $1000 $00 it says that
Your price. $700 from It's Hey That's Not
Usually our price. Our Price Starts
at $1000 but happy to chat to see if you are
A good fit. if you are a good fit let's get
On a call. Our partnership team member will be
Happy to get on a call. it will take you
Til the call for you. and it will chat it will
Talk on email like a human being. reply
Understand what the person is saying.
Imagine all of this being automated. We Do
This today for our mentor reach out.
Every time someone posts on Twitter a
new identification person who creates on
AI We Reach Out to That Person Like This
automatically we don't know who it is when
reaches out when the data comes in we
Let's validate this with a human in the loop
Allow us to shrink
you when people say
Jobs Will Go Right If It's Not That It's Not
The only direction to fire people
will it be done or there
will be layouts it is just
That as companies grow it always needs more
Ficus religiosa
There is no need for many people here. and that
is a massive advantage for people who are
STARTING BUSINESSES. If You Are an AI Native
Brother, you can tear it. just want you to know
How to Deploy AI in the Right Way. you can
Kill it. This causes a lot of skill paranoia
It hasn’t happened. so much c this is
What Skill
Paranoia Is.
we who am i
What Skill
Paranoia Is.
we who am i
What Skill
Paranoia Is.
we who am i
I should learn C skills. Every 6 months I
I learn that it becomes outdated
Because something or the other comes along
Is. Whatever new thing I learned I would get scared
Is. we write anything
that i learn out and
I too have seen two or three jobs going away
Because of this I start to get more scared that oh
[ __ ] now I don't know now I know
No, I can't learn anything because of it
I have been. and just thinking about what
Next what next what next. One
If the month gets delayed then some new idea.
Then something new, then something new, then something new.
Like it's just crazy. bro the reality of
Life is going to be hard. I Came Sadly
don't have a right answer for this and there is
No right answer.  but
what do you think is the
Skills that make people win in today's times
will
give.
Keeping
Up
With
As
I
Am
Being
As
I
Am
will
give.
Keeping
Up
With
As
I
Am
Being
As
I
Am
will
give.
Keeping
Up
With
As
I
Am
Being
As
I
Am
Not Kidding and
How Can People Do It
Can you?  See I think
everybody has to become
Something called AI
generalist.  Yes. So
How does one become
an AI generalist?  Yes.
Like you know so many things about
X and G. I am sure that you will get business
I know how to increase it. How to Creator
I know I have to become great. How to write code
Is. But all this will not be relevant for you.
Maybe some things will be relevant and some won't.
Something relevant to your team. Right?
This much knowledge will not be relevant for you.
So how can everyone learn this in their domain
In? So the World That We're Heading
Towards domain as a thing is of the past. These
whatever
specialist's bug we have
To become a specialist at something.
Go into marketing. go deep into
Marketing. Became head of marketing. Bickham
CMO Yee Wo Yee Wo That is No More a Vice
thing to do any
more okay why do people
Hire People Why Do You Hire People to Solve
What
are
the
problems
with
AI?
What
are
the
problems
with
AI?
What
are
the
problems
with
AI?
you can solve a broad range of problems so
there will be the rise of journalists
90% of what your team will do is upside down
there is 20% journalist and 80% specialist
Your chief of staff is a journalist
your ea is a
journalist there are so who
What are the generalist roles who can do?
a lot of things like we talked about
It will flip. 80% of the roles that will
Exist will be generalist. 20% will be
Specialist. and i believe this is
Those people are majorly specialist roles
I will do consulting. none full time
will remain. Very few people will be there. the reason is us
that's why people are specialist people
I used to say become a specialist because it is
Hard for us to understand and do
Multiple Things as a Human Being. we can
Not just do everything. If everybody
Everyone who is a journalist becomes a founder.
Every founder is a journalist. You know that.
Right? But with AI coming into the picture, you
can actually truly become a great
Journalist. So the word AI journalist is
I believe is that person who can solve any problem
Problems Using AI. That person is an AI
Journalist. it doesn't matter it's a problem
With marketing. it doesn't matter a problem
With product. it doesn't matter it's a
Program Product with Code. Of course,
there are few things that are that
that that that you you you you you you don't touch.
Like, financial probably won't touch it.
Because it's too critical and too not
everything it will be relevant here but you
Get the point I think everyone should become a journalist
Needed AI Journalist Where You Equip The
Using the skills of solving problems
How will AI be created?
I have a road map.  Hmm.
I can give it to you very
quickly.  accept it today
I am a 20 year old. I am Zero AI
In. I don't
know anything.
perfect.  These
In. I don't
know anything.
perfect.  These
In. I don't
know anything.
perfect.  These
After listening to the podcast, like, okay.
Whatever I am doing now I have funds.
perfect. Love it. From Five Levels to This
yes five level to level step by step
Zero this is you are looking at a lot of tools
Are you watching my reels on Instagram
I am watching you, I am watching you in your reels
watching on youtube explore all the
Tools to Understand the Possibilities of AI
what can do today this is level zero like
play with chat gpt play with gemini
play with cloud play with numbers that
AI is on Excel AI is on Excel
There are so many tools, play with all that
Tools because you don't know what you want to
you are a 20 year old but then if you are a
This advice for working professionals
I tell him friend you go down the list, what are the
The Kinds of Things That You Do on an Everyday Basis
level and find the right tool for each of the
Jobs and see how you can do those jobs
faster because that is level zero and
Almost 80% of the work no matter who you are
Raj, your work is also acceptable for you
Shooting Let's See For How Long Because AI
He will do that too in a few days
well but can be automated using
Ai and can be done much better much faster using
ai right if you don't know where the tools are
You need to find it and you will know what the problem is
Have to solve it. there is a platform
called as there is an ai for that.com there
go and put the power point excel data
Analytics it will give you all the list of
Add tools Content Creation All the Content
Be Specific Instagram Reels Video
Editing be specific it will give you because
they have 100s of thousands of tools in the
World. That's the directory. play with
Tools. What will this do at Level Zero?
Your fundamentals will become strong. you understand
I will see what all AI can do. once
You have done this you will get some confidence.
You move to level one. Your Job at Level One
Is for you to crack anything. you need to know
How Things Work. The Reason Why You Crack
Podcasts are because you understand the data
Behind it.  you
understood the humans who
Watch your content behind it. need to
Understand how things work. in level one
What should you do? you understand
I should know how this AI works
does it? How can this LLM work?
Is? He does. What is the back end of it?
How does it give you text? Understand all that. They
After understanding this you should also understand that friend of this
How do we talk together? how do you do it
Prepping? I heard the word by typing
Everyone must have done it. prepping is not right
Poem for me about my dog. there is a way
There is a method to this madness. learn about
Prepping. Every AI tool has a different
Advantage. so inside of a chat gpt so
You might have noticed the
chat is GPT 4.5. us and there
Is one more called s
O3 hum.  what is the
Difference? There is a reasoning model. a text
This is the generation model. Its work which is the 4O model
The work is very different. Emails to all of these
It is very good for. But if your
Have to brainstorm. you should go to O1
And O3 which is a reasoning model. which thinking of
I will tell you. There are a lot of such models
In the world. There are also some open source models.
No code is required for all this.
Need for exploration and excitement
Is required. If you want to see models
You can go to hugging face.com. if you
any platform any ai model which
The whole squeeze out has to be done and all
You have to play with the settings then you can
Go to something called a playground. open
Ai has its own playground. Google's Joe
It's called Google AI Studio.
You don't have any feature in chat GPT
It is available. You input, you get output
Is. All this is internal
Shows customizable features. Temperature,
P value and all that. this will give you a
very good sense of what are the models out
there? How can you prepare with them right? End
A few concepts like rags. you understand
How AI Works on High
Level.
Right
now
in
level
one
and
level
two,
we
have
Level.
Right
now
in
level
one
and
level
two,
we
have
Level.
Right
now
in
level
one
and
level
two,
we
have
I understood how to play with text friend
Do it. but i told you you have to become an
AI Generalist.
Generalist means text only
Does not happen. There are images, videos
it happens, audio happens, all those things come
in. then you should go deep into diffusion
Models like Stability AI Stability
A You Know Comfortable UI is a model of AI
on which you can do stable diffusion and create a
The model with which you can generate images
You can. the level three which is where you go
beside image
you go beside
text we just you
beside image
you go beside
text we just you
beside image
you go beside
text we just you
Texted with LLMs. right now you
you'll go into diffusion models where you
Will you learn how images work? Videos
How does it work? how does audio work
Are? Because when you are solving the problem
Yes, text is not the only problem
Solving you do. You are a generalist.
Remember that.  So how to
make a video from a photo?
will form? How is this
difference created? what are the
Tools to use there? If you like such images
want how did i tell that friend in GBD 4
Go generate the image. then runway ML or
Go to LMA Labs. but don't go to V and Swa
Because they are not good enough. if and a little
If it were advance, I would have said that friend, take care of yourself
make a
model.  we who
already exist
make a
model.  we who
already exist
make a
model.  we who
already exist
There are models. for example what i did
Am. Right? Right? these are all not me
The model has not been created. to existing model
I have trained with my data
That you think like
me.  Think like me. My
Create images like these. all those things are level
Three Where You Go Deep Into Images, Videos
And all that. Infact I will give you a road map
I will give it to you. Detailed road map which you can
Link it up also. if people want to go
Event Paper.  Right?
That is level three. Level
Four. Take these three levels that we did,
this is fundamental understanding of the
The World of AI Out There. right now you
The alphabets have arrived. You got to know the words.
Now it's time to frame sentences and
Right Ass. You Learn How to Build
Products Using AI Right Now. for that
you don't need to know again a single line of
Code. I told you it's a cursor, wind surf
And all that. and now you know how to
Propont. Now you know which model to use.
Now you know how to talk to the models. so you
Can Start Building Products End
Build up product
sense.  Butt still mean
Analytics etc. cannot be done, right? all become
Can. Everything can be done. an eye has an eye can
Right code?  Yes.
so you are so dumb
Good tools are not available which can make it as good
It's software and
apps, not yet available
if it needs to be expanded if you want me
to expand on that
Right Now There Are a Few Constraints AI
hayes
we
are
one
this
is
i
mean
of
course
she
is
very
hayes
we
are
one
this
is
i
mean
of
course
she
is
very
hayes
we
are
one
this
is
i
mean
of
course
she
is
very
It is in early development. Internal
Products that companies are using like
meta and all are much more at once he is with us
There is no access.
Hmm.  But the major problem
with this tools which create softwares
Today is that one which model is used for this
The AI ​​model used inside is all of
They are outdated models. so cursor all this
Which tools do we use in Sonet 3.7 which is
A recent model. J 2.5 has just been released which
is also a recent model. but you know what
Is the best model out there? Open AI I Think
Showed a preview of it six months back.
It's called O3.
We at O3 can
write code as a
It's called O3.
We at O3 can
write code as a
It's called O3.
We at O3 can
write code as a
Top 200 Software Engineers of the World.
so reasoning models are those which are based on thinking
coulda written much better code and when O3
O4 O5 The quality of code will go
Drastically higher is that one. Second Big
the problem is what is called something
Called as context window. A developer who
why is he able to do good work or
Why does experience work quickly?
Developer? Because that one year when I worked in a company
It works, he doesn't understand it
which code what did you do why did you do it
context is the product even if it is not
Million Lines of Code It's the Developer Knows
What is
happening or in
subconscious memory
What is
happening or in
subconscious memory
What is
happening or in
subconscious memory
What is AI? There is something called edge
Context Window of AI: How Much Can It
Remember at once
about anything on a chat
When you open the chat
window, try it sometime
100 pages of content just by copying and pasting
but he will say it can't take so much
content because it can't remember so much
Content at once that is called context
Window which is about 250K 128K tokens
Meaning, take 10,000 words, that's how much it can
remember at once if your code base is 10000
it is more than words so it cannot
remember everything there are rags and all
that's how to do it today
but as you are shooting the
Podcast Two Days Back Mark Zuckerberg
launched
something called
s lama for us
launched
something called
s lama for us
launched
something called
s lama for us
Contact Next Window is 10 million
Tokens.
That means I can go to my developer
I asked brother how big is your code base? 10
Will remain inside million tokens. he said
Vaibhav very easily.
And we are heading towards a world where
There will be unlimited context windows.
Meaning AI can remember whatever you drop
It. If he understood the whole code base
Is. It also has a business logic. why
Can't it write code great?
I will do it myself. So brother, till now we are
He is talking about coding, right?
Talking about it today. Today's
Who is talking about it? today it can
Do MVPs. I am also telling we are all
Talking About the Future and When We Talk
About the future we are not saying that 5
It will happen after a year brother, next year.
I said this much. So much for context window
I spoke about it. Marx will come tomorrow
T-shirt Selfie wearing my black t-shirt
Said 10 million context in the video
The window is done. and we are unlimited
Creating a context window.
Nobody understands this when this tool arrives
After 2 years, understand what will happen and what to do with it
you need then you need to have an
understanding of how to operate the
Systems You Need to Know What Works for You
Need to know what are the best use cases what
is the best way to operate with these models that
You have to build in level four
Things that a 20 year old kid doesn't get a job
I am not feeling it brother, if you are five of Raj's
Five tools to apply together for Raj
Make a caption for what you think can be solved
Could write a new script for Raj
Give ideas from the existing podcast
You can get all the tools without code in just 5 hours
You can make it sitting down, you will not hire it
100% to the guy
that is the dyer needed so you have the skill
sets you apply them build your proof of
Brother work degrees are over to buy oil
gaya degrees there are piece of paper i am
not talking about sea people coming from
IITs, IMS and all there is still to be done
valued and it's not because of where they are
studied it because of how hard it is to
Get into those schools. The Reason Why You Are
Excited to go to Harvard to give a talk.
Was not because that brother means so great
I teach there. that's why you were excited
Because the density of talent is high quality
The talent is very high. it's very hard to
Get in. so those institutes will always
B value. There is no two ways around it.
Anything less than that. Brother everyone is one. it's
All pieces of paper. It's worthless.
Please go and get a degree. I am not
saying don't go and get a degree may be
It will be useful in the future but use your
Bloody Time to Build
Use AI to learn and build, don't rely on it
your education system brother your professors
Who doesn't know what Chat DPD is?
They won't let you use it because they
I think you did the assignment well
You will get your job which they won't
I don't know, that's why I am teaching you
are those people if they had a job they would not be
Teaching in a Regular College
It was still going on because there were enough jobs
He will not stay out. and this is hard
Truth because I am a founder on the other
Side. I know what is happening. and larger
Companies Every Time Metaphors People. their
The stock rises.
Shareholders are rewarded take off because
everybody has realised that the world we are
Heading into is different.
Level five. Level four is done. Now bro level
Five. We spoke about AI agents.
The Future of Teams is Going to Be 20%
Humans are 80% of the AI ​​agents we use
having a research instead of having a
Editor You Will Have AI Agents Working For
you so if you want to be a generalist you have
to learn how to build these AI agents
to automate things like i said mk.com
this that this that you can use tools like na10
Make Lindy zi pier and things like that end
Build Agents Which Can Solve Problems
and unlock your time internal lee na jo jerry
He said whoever makes voice calls, he does it
have the same code name as jerry i have one
Executive Assistant is who checks
My Calendar Which Attends Meetings On
my behavior and gives me notes it attends
every meeting on my behalf if whatever
There is a meeting, I will attend it, my brother
Have you ever looked at the calendar and seen how messed up my life is?
tha because he has to have to be in every bloody
meeting and it was necessary and to me
There used to be a call that maybe something will go now
AI attends my meeting gives me a summary
and and i can just query it saying bhaiya
In the last five meetings, now I mean last
Product Meets in Five Product Sinks
The meetings that happened were in all five meetings
tell me the things that are that
that are repeating five times and we are
Still not solved for it | happened very often
is this and you give me summary of everything
Because AIDS meetings on my behalf.
And I can talk to you about it on my Slack. It
can write emails for all that is fine
Give. Can write email, can reply
yes, can attend the calendar. it can
Execute task right now using op
Using Responses APIF operator. So
it can actually go and do research for me
And give back with a document. it can do
All of that. and these agents know all this
The team has made it, brother. a single line of code
It has not been used. we used a tool called as
Relevance ai and mk.com to be it. I that
I am telling you that as well. Run and read and learn
Do it. If someone can hire an agent for you
will he do it or not? right now at this point of
Time. Any one of the five may hear this
If anything comes after that then come here, I will
I will hire him just like that. and if it does not come
Learn. I will give you the road map below. you learn.
Everybody is capable to do this. You Know
What I am scared of. i am scared of
The Fact That People Will Continue to Stay In
A delusion. They will disagree. give like, hut
Friend, it won't happen like
this.  Hey, I've been here for 5 years
I am studying. I have learned you know the way to
do graphic designing for last seven
Years. what were you doing in the last
Seven Years of Re-Sizing Looking at Dribbble
and replicating that is because that is
What we did most of us. Right? you are kind
Oh friend, I am scared and I feel like it's not right
It will happen like this. I don't want to listen. and this is
What Leads to Drastic Doom. my friend
It is happening together as well, isn't it? I am also a founder
Am. I too am thinking what is this bro
Used to be? You have to embrace it. and you
Will be like how do I win? I am the creator
Am. It is happening to me too. around me
I see people more than me
You can grow faster than me through efficiency
have been. Just because they are using AI
Better. And that is not even there in it.
Or like it's
happening.  it's
Happening.
it
doesn't
scare
me
today
Happening.
it
doesn't
scare
me
today
Happening.
it
doesn't
scare
me
today
I do this
because I am you are
filtering it.  No
I do this
because I am you are
filtering it.  No
I do this
because I am you are
filtering it.  No
it doesn't scare me today because someone
I have not been able to do
it on such a big level.  We
Right? it doesn't scare me because I still have
I am able to outwork everybody. Butt it's over
There will be a problem in a month or two more
Five month, six month.
That is why you also adopt
He is adopting it, right?
so that nobody outworked
You. That's why I am also learning.
That's why I am
also doing things.  The
The real power of AI is original thinking that
Is you as a human being. that's why I
Sed. The Top 10 People Will Always Thrive
Because they are original thinkers. Website AI
Can make it. Butt Joe Website
Meaning the website will be made generic through AI
Because that is what he got as feed. Butt that guy
Website will create a stunning website out of
Brother, he will make a world website and he will earn money
terrible because there is no match because everybody
is making one kind of content and one kind
of website while this guy came out and
Did something outrageously good. he did use ai
but he had original thinking you have to
Build that.  He is
what I have to do this.
I will tell you. I have absolutely no voice in
I didn't know anything
about AI. Right?  end 2
Months ago hit like
what's going on then
This is the world because I was trapped
Abroad Somewhere and I Just Saw Something Like
what is happening when I see you at night
I even called in panic and said, I am you
What are you doing? How is he doing this? this that
How are you doing? That night I got an idea
He had come. That's when I did that experiment
I had started doing it. two days after that
I started
mine.  that video
You sent me.
so is my project
I started it. then i started
thinking bhaiya what's going on since that
till today when my podcast happens
The first hour of the podcast features a video from my team
I sit with you to
understand the right thing
Develop three to four content strategies
They ask questions and they take it right
I have been doing that for the past few years but since
Last two months before this I spent an hour
I have got a separate block in which I am the only one
I flirt with AI one hour every day
I just flirt with AI, that's all
Trying to understand what tools are
what is not there and then the last two months
I found out what a good notebook lm
This is how to do it in studio and everyday
I'm taking an hour off and I'm feeling like [ __ ]
This is what I used to spend six days for
mine works in half an hour and it
just and it's getting better and better and
better and better i will tell you an
what do you think is an interesting thing
Which languages ​​does AI understand?
English AI does not understand any language
it has its own language which we don't
Understand
It's not funny Entropic is a company
The cloud that he
created recently created a
Research was done so that you know this right nobody
Nos How Air Works It's a Black Box
I don't know, I don't
know, even Sam Allman
doesn't know when you send a message that yaar right
A Nice Little Poem
for My Pet Joe Poem
How come nobody understands it was
input in it was trended with a lot of
Content and more like Edge in All
The output that went during training
things started getting better it started getting better
as there was more training in the output
kept getting better but what happens in between
no one knows,
we know that he
predicts the next word that is
Why It's a Generative AI Model But That Too
has been proven and so everything that is false
What we know about AI is our assumptions so
Entropic did this
research that dude is
AI Is Actually Predicting the Next Word
Hum
and
then
they
realise
it
isn't
Hum
and
then
they
realise
it
isn't
Hum
and
then
they
realise
it
isn't
predicting it it actually knows what it is
Wants to say. it arrives at a conclusion
And then makes up everything else.
what are you talking
about?  Right? and in the same
He also understood that friend AI 10 15 20
How is he talking in 100 languages?
We did not even teach
him the language.  C
How is it? I mean we dumped a lot of
Information yes. But how is it working? donation
The realized AI thinks in a language that
That he does not understand me at all. He first his
The person understands the language in his own language.
formulates and then translates
It is available in whatever language you want.
so that is the world that we are living in
Today. Where everything is a black box.
Isn't it scary? Lots of Jobsangi
yaar if this means if
you are telling me that now
I have a large video like you and
I talked to someone for 3 hours after picking it up
Should I put it in the software? Which software?
should I put it where the
cut is made, I mean that is
a mean i'm just
giving a basic outright
software yes opus
clip lets say its ok
I picked it up and put it in it, I said in it
some hype in it, some function in it, some to me
I will have to give a receipt, what will I have to do
House
Opus
cuts
it
off
by
default
for
House
Opus
cuts
it
off
by
default
for
House
Opus
cuts
it
off
by
default
for
example there is something called edge operator
We used to chat on GPT earlier on the computer
created a model
which can handle your
computer but now a new company has come general
Agent Company
We are a
General Agent Company
Agent Company
We are a
General Agent Company
Agent Company
We are a
General Agent Company
General Assembly Company Something Like This I
will get you the right name whatever he does
It also works on other softwares.
so it takes over your browser you just have
to prepare it that friend i need this execution
Have to do it. He will execute it in the back.
I understood that. I am telling you this
that I just posted this on Opposs
Video. I want 25 clips from this
So he will take it out and
give it to me.  we take the shots
will
give.
Yes.
Right?
This
is
the
basics.
yes
basic
will
give.
Yes.
Right?
This
is
the
basics.
yes
basic
will
give.
Yes.
Right?
This
is
the
basics.
yes
basic
Thing.
Yes.
All
will
be
high
performing.
Thing.
Yes.
All
will
be
high
performing.
Thing.
Yes.
All
will
be
high
performing.
it won't happen because it's cutting it at
This point of time.
Good. so it that opus
Is not using his
brain.  not which one
Clip perform? An opportunity. this is it
Can. It's a great idea. I am not
If Opus Is Doing Or Not. Hypothetically speaking
We do.  because c
today 3 hour episode
The genius of the
editor who is with us
works or whatever high performing
podcast knowledge is
that intuition i would
and that knowledge that
brother in these three hours
These 10 things
will work and then
we will cut them
These 10 things
will work and then
we will cut them
These 10 things
will work and then
we will cut them
lets put this AI
can do that right now
No,
intuition
is
trainable,
how
can
you
No,
intuition
is
trainable,
how
can
you
No,
intuition
is
trainable,
how
can
you
How was Creator Intuition created because that
Thousands of clips have been made and pushed
and he has seen which content
worked now if a i has access to your
content it new what the input was and it
New What were the outputs and it's new
What are the pieces that did well in the past
It can build a 100x better intuition
then a video
editor not today
so you today also
then a video
editor not today
so you today also
then a video
editor not today
so you today also
Maybe that's why nobody is making that
A great idea, I will tell you something
hmm right have
you ever seen my
content hmm right
hmm right have
you ever seen my
content hmm right
hmm right have
you ever seen my
content hmm right
in the last three months in actually last
For the last three months I'm not even clocking
The Views That You Do But We Have I Have Done
200 million views on
social everything is ai
That I know 100% is
AI now I will tell you
Where the Real Magic Comes in the Idea
AI also ends the generation
I will tell you how it works there is a
tool
called as
feedly
feedly ok its
tool
called as
feedly
feedly ok its
tool
called as
feedly
feedly ok its
The job is that the RSS feed which is there is every
Time gives new piece of content on the internet
He gets a
ping hmm and
I have given
He gets a
ping hmm and
I have given
He gets a
ping hmm and
I have given
Some
Keywords Hmmm AI
Tech Startups
Some
Keywords Hmmm AI
Tech Startups
Some
Keywords Hmmm AI
Tech Startups
Funding Investment Bunch of Company Names
in India and all of that if anyone
Content Piece Hits The Internet On
any of these keywords are relevant to him
It comes.
Feedly has it all
Is. So Feedly filters this content and
Sends it to an AI for me. He is near the AI
The data is mine of the last 300 videos that
Have posted which
this is a request. So
I send that data using something called edge
mc.com make make m a k e make.com so
Via Make.com we get
the API from Feedly
Which is Chat GPT's API where a
The prompt is
written.  imagine it like
chat gpt butt
automatically
ok ok where
chat gpt butt
automatically
ok ok where
chat gpt butt
automatically
ok ok where
It is written in the form, I gave it to you
I am my boss these 300 pieces of
This is the content which I have posted earlier.
Instagram, Lindin Everywhere Out Of This 300
pieces of content these are the 100 that are
Performed very well. so you know the data
About me on what has worked and what hasn't
work. A new content piece has just arrived. Late
About Urban Company from . do you think
This will go viral. how much would you rate it
from a
scale of one
to 10 if we
from a
scale of one
to 10 if we
from a
scale of one
to 10 if we
He rates the rating himself. AI Systems
rates it. If that rating is more than that
Then that's what happens when I ping in my Slack
Is. New Topic Idea Discovered Urban
Company launched maid services in Mumbai for
₹9 Potential to go viral 9 out of 10 if
That's less than seven. It comes in my sack
Not there. because i
don't want to see this
Where did Urban Company come from? I am I am
Giving an example
does not mean so I get
You put this startup on that Feedly
that that that then from mk.com like how does this
I decided that this
one because he has mine
Data is the kind of content that I have
created in the past the scripts of each
Which topics did one of them perform?
Are? Which topics were not performed
Is?
So
take
that
from
Feedly
and
pay
on
Make
Is?
So
take
that
from
Feedly
and
pay
on
Make
Is?
So
take
that
from
Feedly
and
pay
on
Make
Will go. It will automatically choose the make
Three-four names.  No.
No. Should I redo it?
or
ok.
See
how
idea
generation
happens
or
ok.
See
how
idea
generation
happens
or
ok.
See
how
idea
generation
happens
of my content. Feedly is a platform that
Scrapes the internet for new
Topics.
Yes,
its
okay.
that's
his
job
Topics.
Yes,
its
okay.
that's
his
job
Topics.
Yes,
its
okay.
that's
his
job
That's it. Right? every time give a new
the topic that comes on a topic that I am
Interested in Feedly that data via Make.com
Make.com is like a glue from one
Software to each other without writing code.
Ok?
That's
the
equivalent
of
chat
from
Make.com
Ok?
That's
the
equivalent
of
chat
from
Make.com
Ok?
That's
the
equivalent
of
chat
from
Make.com
goes to gpt.
Ok? that chat gpt
I have written it in writing. And
that's the job of the prophet to tell you brother this is the
Content that I have done in the past. these are
This is the content that has work topics that
have work. these are the topics that have not
Worked.
we
are
based
on
this
data
Worked.
we
are
based
on
this
data
Worked.
we
are
based
on
this
data
You tell me this topic according to your intuition
has just arrived how much would you rate it from a
On a scale of
one to 10 we.
So AI rates that
On a scale of
one to 10 we.
So AI rates that
On a scale of
one to 10 we.
So AI rates that
Topic from a scale of one to 10. if he
Which is the rating for that topic from seven
Is too much. because everyday is 100s of peace
Less content. I can't create content or
Everything. So if it is more than the intake
Then this is the summary of this piece of content
Pings me in my Slack. New
Content idea form in this case urban
Company launches the
₹9 maid service wherever
Right? Then he looks after my personal team there.
Everyday some 10-15 pieces of content like
Ideas like this come up in my Slack.
Comes on its
own.  Automatically
automated right?
Comes on its
own.  Automatically
automated right?
Comes on its
own.  Automatically
automated right?
Skim through 100s of articles. My Team
From here it picks up the topics and gives
Just Select Agree Disagree Agree
Disagree Good Not Good Good Not Good We Pick
about three to four topics here this pic
Having said that we have an AI agent system
It is made, what is the first step in it
how to write a script
writes again I have fed a lot of
Scripts That Have Worked in the Past
that has gone viral so it knows how I write
Scripts | so it is able to mimic my
script
writing hmm so
this topic goes
script
writing hmm so
this topic goes
script
writing hmm so
this topic goes
He does deep research on the topic
The step one is researching about this topic.
We use Perpsity's API. again
No code nothing is needed. A bit bigger than the API
The document comes from research about this
Topic. This research goes into my prep
which is which has been fed up with all the
Articles and all the Lindin posts and reels
That has gone viral in the past. so it knows
what will work, what will not work. So
He writes scripts from three angles and
He writes five hooks of each angle.
Ok.
Then a Human in the Loop Comes in Where We
Select which hook combinations do we like
And after being selected, in the diffuse model
goes where my AI clone is made
clones my video to 11 labs
and goes to the smallest ai where
My audio is cloned and both are merged
Both come with infotainment and video editor
goes to. every piece of content that
Comes out has one body five hooks.
So these are the 100s of pieces of content that we
What did you bring from outside? One body, three, four hooks.
Now I have five or six dummies with this content
The profiles
are there.  we
we put it there.
The profiles
are there.  we
we put it there.
The profiles
are there.  we
we put it there.
Let's check the initial matrix by putting it.
What is the first three second view? What
Is it the retention rate? what is the view to
Share rate? Let's see which hook it is
He is
performing the
best.  Hum and We
He is
performing the
best.  Hum and We
He is
performing the
best.  Hum and We
Have a benchmark. This is not automated.
This is manual today. if that benchmark
cross will happen then we put this video on
Instagram If That Benchmark Isn't Crossed
then we pick up the right hook and post on
hoga we don't put that video on Instagram
wow wow
as a result
From again I am not the creator, he is yours
Who also knows it. I like to experiment
I have a lot of fun. Right? this was a
Experiment for me
wild. in 3 months
From 200K right now it's at 600K
Followers English Content Tech Content Average
Views Per Reel Is 350K Views One Out Of
Three Reels Hits a Million Views on a 500
K Account with only
English Content Dam
all i and how much time do i spend
doing this 10 minutes a day
sick this is insane
So many people are creating AI content
many people its not even funny i don't know
anyone who has grown as fast as I have
Because they have an inherent creator marketer brain
Also,
what is the
correct
data date
Also,
what is the
correct
data date
Also,
what is the
correct
data date
Joe Experimenter
Inherently Data Experimenter
Everybody can do what you have been doing for so many years
Intel has developed, not sure what will shine
What will work
is finding
patterns that give
What will work
is finding
patterns that give
What will work
is finding
patterns that give
you as over every aspect so that too is one
That edge is needed. that story telling,
Copywriting, Understanding, People,
A little bit of psychology is needed. If You
are you a fast track it, people, other people can
also do it. It will take them a year.
Correct.
No
matter
how
much
air
he
uses
throughout
the
year
Correct.
No
matter
how
much
air
he
uses
throughout
the
year
Correct.
No
matter
how
much
air
he
uses
throughout
the
year
It will work. Because when you ask in simple
word, when you are speaking, five hokks and a
body, when you ask in the beginning, six
It will take seven months to get it right
Which you will remove from
robotics.  We are correct.
And for a creator that one month cycle
Hoagie Max.
Correct. That is
right.  friend and a
Hoagie Max.
Correct. That is
right.  friend and a
Hoagie Max.
Correct. That is
right.  friend and a
There is an insane opportunity in this. we are
Living in a World Ware Distribution
is going to be the most premium asset we
Right with AI you can multiply
Content
Creation Hum It Makes
Every Sense In
Content
Creation Hum It Makes
Every Sense In
Content
Creation Hum It Makes
Every Sense In
The World to Start a Production Company
Content companies such as companies that make movies
150-200
creators
150-200
creators
150-200
creators
give on
which basically their followers their views
Everything will be owned by you. so technically
Who doesn't even
exist.  you can do that age
well. You Can Create Creators Who Don't
Exist.
Random
Phases.
or
generate
phases
Exist.
Random
Phases.
or
generate
phases
Exist.
Random
Phases.
or
generate
phases
Massive opportunity.
How to generate faces
will it be generated? AI will
do it.  This will do it friend.
It is mid journey.
Great tool.  Random Show Bun
will
go.
have
you
seen
this
videos
of
mind
will
go.
have
you
seen
this
videos
of
mind
will
go.
have
you
seen
this
videos
of
mind
where i look like harrypotter, iron man and
My team does all this? Experiments. so we
People have been making AIDS using it for two years
AI Two Years From Now
Right Now You Can Face It
By swapping to anything and generating a photo
So we can create a completely realistic human
That which move sends everything through the process
also is very simple you go to a tool like
Mid journey and right now the chat is GPT's four
Image Generation is Incredible
You will get the right photo realistic image there
Say by giving the right preparation on how you
Want the Character to Be the Advantage Here Is
You can also say that this is the character
I want it with five sides too. Same Face
I want it retained in 100 dresses also. all come
Will
go.
Fully
free.
now
take
this
image
and
Will
go.
Fully
free.
now
take
this
image
and
Will
go.
Fully
free.
now
take
this
image
and
Go To A Platform Like Llama Labs Dream
Machine.
LMA
Labs
Dream
Machine
and
Machine.
LMA
Labs
Dream
Machine
and
Machine.
LMA
Labs
Dream
Machine
and
Runway ML Hum
and Sora
Sora Is Not That
Runway ML Hum
and Sora
Sora Is Not That
Runway ML Hum
and Sora
Sora Is Not That
Great.
I
am
waiting
for
VO2
which
Great.
I
am
waiting
for
VO2
which
Great.
I
am
waiting
for
VO2
which
This is Google's
model.  which which has the
The ability to convert an image into a life
Off a video.
because Lum is doing a runway machine from the lab
Is. Sora does it too but not as well
It is there right now. but ya de incredible that what
Can do it today. I can't even think of it
What will you become in 2 years, brother?
Tear or Wild? and also the videos themselves
All will be done. Do I tell you something? I
Means I don't know if you thought about it like
This?
I have investors. You have investors.
I have a GPT
where I feed everyone
conversations that I have with my
investors which is only with me
Obviously
where
I
was
before
let's
go
today
Obviously
where
I
was
before
let's
go
today
Obviously
where
I
was
before
let's
go
today
I am having a board meeting, I can upload a copy of the deck
I get on a
voice mode and I say
Grill Me Like An Investor
on voice mode and it wears the hat off to this
The grilled investor looks at the numbers
The context is what I did earlier
It has happened before and after seeing these numbers
grills me in the call so that's you
Prepared for the next investment I am
prepared for whatever if i
The investor meeting is after 2 hours.
Brother, put on earphones before 2 hours
I am grilling
myself wow this is what
What you can do when you apply for a job as
well of course right that the interviewer
will ask yes
And even before your podcast I think I am
I am because you know when you do a
Podcast like this you said yaar will geek
on ai and all of that i thought this is something
The fund will ask fundamental questions. Lot of
Times We Miss Out on Fundamentals Only
Because we think we know it. and I'm doing something wrong
Should I say no? So I said friend, I
I am doing a podcast with Raj. it's
Going to be business, AI and all of that.
Ask Me the Most Fundamental Questions
Where You Think Most of the Humans Will Go
Wrong. Guess my answer. tell me how
Can I improve it? and if something is wrong
He said, remind me. in the end a report
Send it to me so I can read it.
so it started asking me simple
Questions What is quantum computing?
What are Qubits? What is GPT?
What is a transformer? and then I
I started to give answers and I liked it
Boss, I had to think for everyone. Me
Do you know what it is subconsciously? But
That became my must practice.
So we I do this quite a lot. this is
Like a hack. And let me tell you another hack. For
All the people who are trying to learn. Djent
Matter right? This is what we are talking about
So you can do it in interview also. Job
Put a description and tell me friend
Actor and Interviewer and Interview
I am applying for this role in the company
I am applying for
this old one of mine
This is a resume and this is the job description
is the person who I am going to interview me
Here is this
Lindin profile
take action now
Here is this
Lindin profile
take action now
Here is this
Lindin profile
take action now
Like Raj Samani and grill me for this
interview and ask me the toughest of the
toughest questions
give me answers also
yes if I don't if I
if i say it wrong give me answers also so
that i know what is
the right answer hum
Incredibly powerful and one that does a lot
Hi Raj and I will also recommend you to it
I don't if you do this. Google AI Studio
There is a platform. there is an option
To share your screen in real time.
So, I don't know coding. I Keep
Playing with all these open source repositories
And all. and i get stuck because
I don't know coding. so i can share
My Screen with Google AI Studio End
I can literally talk to it. and he guides me
Will do it. Click on this button. may be this is
Wrong. try this option because it can see
Your screen. it is on a video call with you
aai which means bhaiya it uses 2.5 so which
Is the one of the smartest model multi
is a billion parameter model. he is with you
Making a video call. no video of it
Is. Making an audio call. Your Screen
looking at you and talking with you and
He is saying what should be done? Future Can
There must be a better teacher than this?
How Crazy and Wild Word That We Are
Living in? All of these are possible today. End
These are my learning tools bro. [ __ ]
This is how I learn nowadays. YouTube video
It comes. I don't have patience YouTube
to watch the video. joe rogan podcast
Gone, your podcast has arrived. interesting
It is topic. But I'm on the go. I have this
10 things to
know.  What?  what
should you do? These
10 things to
know.  What?  what
should you do? These
10 things to
know.  What?  what
should you do? These
Take.
Pick
up
the
podcast.
Go
to
Emily.
there
is
a
Take.
Pick
up
the
podcast.
Go
to
Emily.
there
is
a
Take.
Pick
up
the
podcast.
Go
to
Emily.
there
is
a
Platform called Meetly. AI you go there.
You drop the video and you start chatting
With the video.
Chatting means what?  Chatting
means let's say, hey, like, let's say this
Podcast Someone Picks It Up and Drops It.
And it gives you a nice little summary saying
They are talking about AI, they are talking
About all this tools and all. And let's say
Notebook LM which you mentioned has arrived.
what is notebook lm that raj is what is
Notebook LLM? Can you tell me what that is?
it will explain and will give a time
Stamp. You click on it. it will play the
Video Exactly Where You Are Saying
Notebook LM. so that will give you the
Explanation there.
So this is in our
there is no need because where such words
There is an option below it.
We are not needed
either.  our ward's
There is no need, brother. right there right there
The option comes up. The Notebook alum will be dropping by, too.
Whatever that is, that will also come. how to use
You can, he will also come. right there this is us
Let's put it in the edit. but i will tell you
Where I use it actually. Technical Content
Whatever happens, I need to understand it, my friend
What is. But I understood it in the video
I am not coming. because two engineers talk
are doing it.  They're
geeking out. but to me
I have to understand. Pick up the video, upload it and ask the question
Start asking questions
on it.  there is a voice
mode also. so i came many many many many many many many many
many can turn on the voice i can play talk
with that youtube video now this is all
possible these are my learning tools now i
Di has attention span not reading blog articles
I am sorry but that is what I am afraid of
This is my condition, this is the condition of the children
What will happen
It's you who have scared me the whole podcast
I feel like I'm so far behind
I feel like I don't even know
What in the world don't I have an hour 5
You will have to devote hours every day just to learn
all the same no yaar i
think its a kick kick
Start problem. the moment you kick
Start, the moment you go in. I passively
I don't sit for hours. because you are
In this world. you are excited about
Every new thing that comes in. aren't you
Get Excited About Topics That You Really
Like, really enjoy. Right? this is how it is
is. I've never been more excited in my
Life. I can tell you this. i can't remember
When last time I was so excited. because
Cracking linden
No, there are faces. You are right. when
When this reel cracking was happening on
Instagram There Was That Face. linden when
Cracks There Was This Face. Butt Boss
What a great time, friend. something every day
You get to learn. how often does this happen
How many times does this happen to you now? No
It happens like this these days friend. but with this has come
In like it's so fun. It is so much fun. But
Scary. tell me three tools that can help you
Small business owners should use it.
Small Business Owner. which is a small problem today
We are not talking about AI revolution in the world
We do. AI AI is coming. Very
There are buzzwords. but when i talk to my dad
I do it in Indore, what is it with them
These? They only know that I just
Taught him the
problems of a business.  I
I am telling you the same thing. So now they know it
That he is sitting on top on WhatsApp. From there
Ask what is the itinerary for going to Dubai
Is. So he would make a three day idea.
Is. That's for those use cases. Right?
And only if someone sends something in English
would you go there or convert it to hindi
Two. So it will convert it into Hindi.
That's that use case. Now I love them and my
Millions of Indian Business like Papa
Owners who may be a small grocery store
shop or trading business or
It is a manufacturing business. that business
Is. Right? Small Business Meaning
From earning ₹10,000 a month to ₹100 crore
Till I earn a month. Ok? Small Business Bol
I have been them. How do they use AI today?
and expand your business
Because those people are the most affected
will go because they are one with technology
So this conversation doesn't even reach there
Even if they reach there then they feel that today
So far your system is very good
Our system will
remain which lots of people
have survived a lot of stuff, that means
If they also survive e-commerce
what should they do man look this is very
Broad Questions Say It Is Very Hard To
Answer this and I will tell you why this answer
To do that I need their specific top
You will have to know the problems because blanket
If anyone wants to
increase their money, no problem
what is what is not along with you
To grow sales
have to be increased
look let's say okay
i will go deeper you
You are asking me if I want
to increase sales by one person
Take a person and solve it for him
will give me a
person grocery store
hey my ok what
are you selling
all the things
hey my ok what
are you selling
all the things
hey my ok what
are you selling
all the things
Whatever is sold in
the grocery store.
Correct.  Now no one
Whatever is sold in
the grocery store.
Correct.  Now no one
Whatever is sold in
the grocery store.
Correct.  Now no one
I am facing trouble because of work.
Correct. You have to
grow your business.  Right?
so the first thing that i will do is that i
Don't get into Will Advise Them is AIY.
First a nice WhatsApp announcement
Start the channel.
we where the
people who are with you
Start the channel.
we where the
people who are with you
Start the channel.
we where the
people who are with you
Do they come to buy things, their phone
You add the number to the announcement group
You will go.
Ok? and every time you have a new
Will the product arrive or will you order it at some time?
Will you run a discount or will you make small deliveries
You will start making announcements in the group
You will tell all the customers about you
You will find out and
you will be top of mind.
This is the bare minimum everyone should do
Right and now when you make this announcement
Group You Will Need Marketing Materials
Do you want to put a plate or a new menu?
You have to upload the image of the product for that
Obviously you can go to chat gpd via voice
you can press the button and say that
Brother send me such message on your WhatsApp
You should write it in English in the group.
Mango season is
here.  Mango season
Alphazo is Mango.  It has
arrived just today. Now!
Arrived in stock. I have 10 kilos.
Make a nice image and a price.
Write the message in English. price is so much
Is. He will give it. You copy paste it. Chat
GPT should also not be used. Using WhatsApp
Your answer will also be
available in Meta.  Also meta
Create an image.
Create a meta image as well
will take it. if you want a good image but for that
That is a lot. Meta image should also be good
Will
go.
Ok?
Right?
The
third
thing
you
do
Will
go.
Ok?
Right?
The
third
thing
you
do
Will
go.
Ok?
Right?
The
third
thing
you
do
you can, that is, if
What speaks to you a lot? Maintaining an account
It depends on you. Who owes how much?
What is? Everything around it. And your
It is written
all over the
paper.  Hmm.  Right?
It is written
all over the
paper.  Hmm.  Right?
It is written
all over the
paper.  Hmm.  Right?
And papers get lost and wander about. For him
How will you manage it? all the days that you
You write, take the end of the day photos.
Keep taking photos and not all the photos in one chat
Put it in the GPT window and say that
Friend, please make a final table for me
Two
and the old data is of that old which
There is a photo and this is a new photo, all of them are one
Make a table, I
will make an
account book for you
Make a table, I
will make an
account book for you
Make a table, I
will make an
account book for you
That
account
book
will
continue
to
be
made
for
which
That
account
book
will
continue
to
be
made
for
which
That
account
book
will
continue
to
be
made
for
which
will keep you watching
You can do these small things when you are small
It's your business, you can do all of this
Nice. Or you can even tell it on voice
That I made this bill. so many rupees for this
are on loan. Put it
in his account.  His
Put it in the account. to his account
Put it in.  That can't
happen right now. because you
I will have to build it. You will need a custom GPT
Will have to make it. Which if you don't know.
Your son will come. tell it on youtube
I want to make an app.
Vaibhav sir had said
Or Raj had said GPT in chat GPT
Have to make it.
We will find out by
doing that on YouTube
Have to make it.
We will find out by
doing that on YouTube
Have to make it.
We will find out by
doing that on YouTube
How can you make a small app and that
He will make the app for you.
No, because kids are very dependent on the internet right now.
There are. He will
figure it out.  Tax
We will take it somewhere or the
other.  you might be on youtube
I will make it after
watching a video.  yes no bro
So you should also watch some videos on YouTube.
It is not that difficult. Voice
I just have to send it to you. there is a tool
Called a scale AI which is calorie AI.
Brother, a 20 year old kid has made this tool
To. Without writing a single line of code.
Tell me how much is the revenue of the app? 30 million.
What does You Know app do?
eat after watching the food
Will you take a photo of? After taking the photo he
Estimates calories based on how the
Food is looking. It is a dead simple app for
Anyone to make. The guy knows distribution
how to do it.
App Marketing App
Marketing is here.  My
Who needs it too. Brilliant
Look at this madness. there is a guy called
S level sao. You must have seen Indkar on Twitter
We
guys
have
created
a
flight
simulation
app
We
guys
have
created
a
flight
simulation
app
We
guys
have
created
a
flight
simulation
app
Made a simulator game. All Using AI
Ranking and Money The Guy Does is a Solo Opener. I
don't know how many companies you started
He knows a little coding. But just wipe it now
Coding does that. Wipe Coding Is
Essentially Prepping and Getting a Product
Out. The Guy Does $ Million Dollars In
Revenue. Lex Fritt Band podcast
I went to.
$ Million in Revenue Single Person.
Because you are talking about business. I am
Telling you this. there are so many
Opportunities. there are jobs which are
Meaning if there are no jobs it doesn't mean anything
Is. There is no
opportunity.  brother lots of
There are problems. This is very interesting.
Ok? those who are entrepreneurs, who
I think friend, I have to make something big and that's it.
When we both were starting. hand in
Your heart. Ok? Hand on your heart. V
didn't want to do anything which can't
Be built into a billion dollar company. yes and
No? Because our aspiration was that friend
There is a revenue of $200 million to be made.
1500 crore revenue needs to be generated so that
Become a
unicorn.  Do
this correct.
these these
Become a
unicorn.  Do
this correct.
these these
Become a
unicorn.  Do
this correct.
these these
Entrepreneurship was for us. now it has
Revolve for you for me
everybody.  but there
is this category that no one is showing
Was. You Know Building 10 Businesses Doing $
million
It is much easier than building one business which
Will do $1 million. Building 10 Businesses
What will $1 million do is much easier than that
Building One Business Which Will Do $10
Million. And the inside of this is that brother you
Learn a SOP which can make 1 million or 1
Could make crores. Let's say right? Those SOPs and
Where can it be applied? New You Don't
Need new insights. you need to learn how to
Replicate the model in different places. You
If you replicate then easily it is much easier
that friend you will create 10 businesses one by one
One crore rupees will be given in one month
Business which
can earn 10 crores
is fair and this
Business which
can earn 10 crores
is fair and this
Business which
can earn 10 crores
is fair and this
is a bit trajectorist because of AI
Because that is the product development cycle
It is much faster now. need customer support
Brother will run the AI ​​agent. Marketing Material
Brother, I want an AI agent by making a template
will run it. Before this you need 10 teams. You
Don't need it anymore.
you need probably like you know 10 years for
You to manage each of the businesses with a lot of
Agents. That too a very interesting
There is an opportunity. and today because this is india
A maker who is a solopreneur
Who can build a very sizable business. this which
This is the biggest opportunity. From this
Previously If You Think About It creators were one
Who were able to create content reach out to
Millions of people and make very good money. But
How many creators can there be in India?
I will beat the education creators around
like high quality creators the people that
I consume not more than 10 in fashion and
There will be 15-20. The whole ecosystem is mixed together
200 top grade creators in the country
That's it or will
there be more?  too much
1000 to 2000.  OK
2000 for the country of
Size of 140
crores.  now
that is the
Size of 140
crores.  now
that is the
Size of 140
crores.  now
that is the
Opportunity. There are only 2000 slots
And 5000 slots from Let's Make It. Now
We are talking about 1% creators who earn money
Will earn. How much
1 lakh per month? how many creators are in
India who makes 10 lakhs per month? according to
To you?
how much do you think? you who right now
2000 said everyone must be earning 10 lakhs. If
How much will it be if it is made 10 lakhs? On 1 crore
Year. How many people will
there be? 1000 people.  people so
Must be earning.
₹ 1 crore per year.
1000 people.  The
Must be earning.
₹ 1 crore per year.
1000 people.  The
Must be earning.
₹ 1 crore per year.
1000 people.  The
Chances of you making 1 crore by becoming a
The creator is 1000 by 2
what billion people
140 crore 140 crore
people 1000 by 140 crore
People is your odd to make 1 crore becoming a
Creator Pathetic Odds It's the Worst
decision ever you get my point what is a
Higher odds are you wanting to earn 1 crore in a year?
How much is Crore by 12 months
about 8 lakh 8 la 8
lakh yes 8 la by 1000
how much did it cost
correct
yes
if you can build a product
Where 800 people give you
₹1000 1000 a month you
Make More Money Your Odds of Building a Very
Micro niche product may be something for you
very specific niche of people lets say a
Specific
landlord
we
are
very
specific
niche
that
you
landlord
we
are
very
specific
niche
that
you
landlord
we
are
very
specific
niche
that
you
Understand and make a product for them
You can. there are 100s of thousands of
Micro opportunities like this one
The entrepreneur does not see. because
The entrepreneur who thinks I want to make something
He thinks his brother is worth 100 million dollars
Have to generate revenue. Ok? which is a
The agency that runs what many people think
yes brother team business is all about a lot of
People don't look at this idea. because that
They say, friend, this
is not very small.  it's
Not worth it.  But a
Solopreneur Today All
By himself can build it.
We will be podcasters only who will pay ₹1000
I'll give you a month's give you go
Micronesia Find Micronesia and Their Truth
a large opportunity man give me three
Ideas This Should Be My Last Question
because i ask everyone three
Ideas for three business ideas that no one can earn today
You can also start as a solarpreneur
Exact niche idea I think one as a
Soulpreneur You Can Build An Automation
Agency
What
are
we?
This
is
automation
agency
Agency
What
are
we?
This
is
automation
agency
Agency
What
are
we?
This
is
automation
agency
It happens that friend, there is AI here, like AI
is all over the place but
Nor can big companies go to TCS
can go to wipro anywhere
can to get to get to companies to
execute solutions for them but these are 100
Your company
is of 40 people
can you help with it you can learn it yourself
You don't have
time to say this
I was going to be an AI trainer, is there any
Me
yes
correct
so
AI
agency
is
a
very
Me
yes
correct
so
AI
agency
is
a
very
Me
yes
correct
so
AI
agency
is
a
very
Interesting Arbitrage That Exists
Because all the medium to small companies don't
Have a solution today. Massive Opportunity Edge
A Solarpreneur If You Know Five Different
Three Four Different Tools Make ZPier Off
Of Course You Need to Know How to Do Prepping
Needed? What are models? Make Zpier N10
Relevance AI Lindy Crew AI So many tools
Are. You have pretty good automation and agents
You can make
it.  Ok?  He
became one. I
You can make
it.  Ok?  He
became one. I
You can make
it.  Ok?  He
became one. I
Think Like a Solarpreneur
You can build a vibe coding a platform
I mean not platform a vibe coding
studio
vibe coding studio that's it man you you
Come and tell me what this research is
No, it is taking me a lot of time to find such a tool
Can you make a personal software? I need it
which only i
will use us
and you also know that it can be done without
Code but don't want to put in the effort. there
There could be lots of vibe coders who are very good
We're talking to someone
who can build personal AI
Solutions that only
you will use.  yes like
my own my habit and gold
I need a tracker
exam there you go there
I will make it for you. 2 lakh, 3 lakh, whatever
He will charge it and make it for you.
How much time will it take? It is also 5 hours. Djent
Matter.
If
You
Know
How
to
Wipe
Code
Really
Matter.
If
You
Know
How
to
Wipe
Code
Really
Matter.
If
You
Know
How
to
Wipe
Code
Really
well. Right? this is a very interesting
opportunity which i am talking broad
Opportunity because I don't know the guy
What does it
do.  or
right and third
third we this
What does it
do.  or
right and third
third we this
What does it
do.  or
right and third
third we this
Right butt will be a little difficult for solo runner
I think its a very interesting opportunity
It exists. Don't be a solo runner
Can. A small team will have to be formed for this
For which is service as a software line.
we are so for example
Your bank is late, right?
If there is a problem then he calls
And if it is Airtel then you are right you have a problem
you call the telephony and you will wait for 10
After waiting for half an hour someone will press the button
will connect with humans a little and most of the
Times That Humans Are Not Smarter Than You
They just have an SOP to follow, they know
If the customer says this, then say this, say that
It happens.
This opportunity exists as a service as a
Software.
You can build an agent and there are lots of them
Tools to Do That Again for Smaller Businesses
Let's talk to customer support or a customer
Just take the support. Ok? where you are a
You can create a voice agent using a tool like
Vapey right? right very easy to build that
Where anyone can call me. For
Example: In the same case, you call Airtel
Will do it. instead of putting any number because
you are talking to ai you can talk directly
to it and tell your problem and his
The knowledge base is already fed to you
I will give you the solution. this call used to cost
₹15 per minute to a company like Airtel. it's
Very expensive.
That is that can go away. The Reason Why I
said it's not just software is because in
These cases, right? What happens? there will
B cases which are beyond the knowledge base which
R edge cases. There Human in the Loop has to
kick in.
So if you
have 100 people
kick in.
So if you
have 100 people
kick in.
So if you
have 100 people
There is a team of 10 people, let's end it
you have this software and you put that
the logic that anything beyond this question it
Should come to a human automatically. then you are
Able to set up a service as a software
Business. And enable multiple solutions
which was not accessible before.
Companies which were not able to hire a
Customer Support Team Because It's Too
Expensive for them. you can be the sussion
For them.
Because
absolute arbitrage
For them.
Because
absolute arbitrage
For them.
Because
absolute arbitrage
Absolute Arbitrage
Wild.
That's
one
more.
but
this
solo
prone
Wild.
That's
one
more.
but
this
solo
prone
Wild.
That's
one
more.
but
this
solo
prone
You won’t be able to do
it.  Big team, small team
should would.  And a big
BD team will be required.
yes i mean ya but the beauty is bhaiya tere ko
You don't need only two clients, do you?
What did you say while sitting with 100 clients?
want to make 1 crore want to make 2 crore 10
If you want to make crores then don't talk about 100 million
Do it if you have to make 100 million
Scale you can not be a sole pints very
very hard but i
could be locking as well
can people sam
allman you know what he
said
yes
that
1%
billion
dollars
said
yes
that
1%
billion
dollars
said
yes
that
1%
billion
dollars
company is
going to be
happening or if you
company is
going to be
happening or if you
company is
going to be
happening or if you
Look at Mid Journey which is an image generator tool
A team of 30 people is worth $200 million
generates revenue
A cursory same 25 members same $ million
Dollars in revenue it's happening right in
in front of
us it's wild
Thank you so much, you have turned my head
Now I will learn from you separately.
it was really
Great to talk to you after so long there
is a background story guys me and vaibhav
how you met
So Vaibhav was king on Lindin
[Laughter]
I used to sell Lindin corsairs now and
Lindin it cracked itself so
Lindin was very trendy and then it was made
Courses on how to grow Lindin is an add on
After seeing this I messaged Vaibhav
we meet
before that
no one knows
o is it me
we meet
before that
no one knows
o is it me
we meet
before that
no one knows
o is it me
I messaged you, then I started talking
I had some 400-500 followers and so did Vaibhav.
There were only a few
around that no I had 2000
2000 both of us then I messaged and
I talked to Vaibhav
and he told me not to
tell
And that's what we made, we said that good company
I am all people so we made a group
Where there was splendor, I was Varun, there was a lot of illusion
All of us were creator friends and all of us
had decided that friend we will become everything
I want to move forward in life
And this group had only one specialty
That was all these entrepreneurs first
The creators were second and all businesses had to be created
No one wanted to be a content creator but
At that time TikTok
was banned and reels
When it started we all created a WhatsApp group
But we decided to do one thing. Reel
New thing arrived. One reel every day.
everyday
Will make a
reel.  Oh my
God.  and put
Will make a
reel.  Oh my
God.  and put
Will make a
reel.  Oh my
God.  and put
and whatever you will learn from it every 30 days
We will share with each other what we have learned
What did we not learn so that everyone can become better.
And by the way we became
friends.  and from then to today
Till then Vaibhav made the reels in it, Varun
Made it. No, this story is a bit dull
Is. real story is
We all started making reels. I am 15 days
After that I gave up. I don't know Varun
After how many days did you give up but Raj
I did not give up at all. Right? as a result
hee groo hee groo you groo you groo and you
Got to like I think a million followers.
And I don't know if you remember this.
Mumbai house before starting the podcast
We sat down and brainstormed
And you asked me, brother, what can I do?
Are? So I called you my friend creator
can make a podcast of this
Can make it. then i will ask you a question
I asked you, I remember it very well
When I asked you friend how will he do this?
How will you ask questions? I don't know
How it works. Nothing, brother, we both
We will talk just as we are talking.
There will be two cameras. It literally happened today.
Now the thing is different where you are at
Probably 8 million 7 million subscribers
on YouTube with the podcast and I'm so
bloody proud of you
my brother thank you
thank you but that's this story that day it
started on a group from then till today a
Not a day goes by when I don’t create content
that's true not a day
has passed and that's
how started and vaibhav started
Building a company to since then Vaibhav has
there has not been a day where vaibhav stopped
Building a Company So He Is Also Growing
I'm growing and I just look back
Like varun also growing. Everybody is growing
yes brother. Prakhar was in it. Intense Grow Eye
Was like wow. what does it say? what does
From it?  Value
CC Value Content
A group was formed
by creators.  no no
What does it say about people.
It's just that everybody can do it. V
Just give up none of
us there.  we always
Try to find it. that's the great part
About that group,
right?  All of them have
Different.
Everybody
did
everything
differently.
Different.
Everybody
did
everything
differently.
Different.
Everybody
did
everything
differently.
And by the way, everyone has seen failures too
Are. If you look at Varun, he failed to build it
Happened. Then after that a very massive outcome was created
Took it. You started two or three things and they failed
Hui. Figured out pet and made something else.
I started and failed. some other
Made the thing. Then I failed, then I failed again. Then
Like we all failed back to back. between
Prakhar started it and it stopped. Then
Started it and then stopped. then start
Like
and
every
time
we
failed.
We
Spoke
Like
and
every
time
we
failed.
We
Spoke
Like
and
every
time
we
failed.
We
Spoke
With each other.  or
some form and passion and
Varun came, okay? and he was also
talking. I was speaking to Vaibhav about
This and we all had like the same trauma. sometime we
Sometimes abusing people, sometimes himself
Sometimes they are abusing, sometimes they are abusing the team
Sometimes they are abusing the investors.
We have done
everything in this.  between
Everyone is raising money together in crypto.
NFT gift money to my [ __ ]. at night
Waking up at 2:00 am trying to buy an NFT
have been.
Oh [ __ ]. Times. but good stuff yaar since then we
All have been kept and I am so proud of that
They are bursting something or the other. like just look at
This
Like it's just insane that none of us top
Different fields none of us stocked. So
That's why me and Vaibhav go long back and
It just happens. These podcasts also happened like this
Vaibhav one day called me and said I want to do this
Am. I am doing this. and they like ya
ok let's do it. like it has never been
Anything else. Yes. so it's an eye feel
Extremely proud. I enjoy it a lot
that when I started my company one of
The First Investors Vaibhav Was There. Splendour
started a company one of the investments
First
Investors Are So Funny
Right. I'm your angel investor and you are
My angel.
And it's the same with
Varun as well.  or beans
Same is the case with Varun. we was angel
Investor. It's just and Varun invested
In my company age well. So wow good. Full
cycle full full cycle all of them to each other
We are growing together. Still Intel
still we have a sounding
board it and it's so for me the lesson is
That
whatever who you are today find people like
You. So something or the other is on the same journey.
You don't know how it will all explode
And they can share so
much intel with each other
I say one thing it's not like people like
You. I don't think we did that. I Think We
had this feeling you correct me if i am
why at least i had the feeling that
Everyone in the group I thought they were smarter
then me and I thought I would learn from them
for me the feeling was i thought everything or nothing
try to do it or i
ft like everybody
is trying to do
something yes and i will
have something to
learn from them or
so i called it for me it was like
everybody is on a
similar journey with me to
Whoever is on the same type of journey, he likes that
At that time, I had friends who
Probably they were 50 times ahead of us. at the same time
But my friends were probably five
The levels will be down. But the strongest
friendship even today is with you guys
Because we were all on
the same level.  Correct.
And even today we all live at the same level.
And they pulled each other. and its
Almost the same level. and also people don't know
This is which I think even you don't know this.
My
my first brand deal which was
Upgrades came, I got
₹0000 and that was the splendor
had given
He did not receive his money for a year
Quick
So it had earlier done a brand deal with Woh & Woh
He did not earn any money after doing the brand deal
wasn't it I think we were talking a lot six seven eight
After a month he did not get the money and its
After I did it, I
got the money and
That gave me the confidence to leave
Indore and come to Bombay, brother make money
Can.  70,000 brand
deals can be made
So anything can
happen.  or so you were my
First Brand Deal Brand Brand Butt
Eventually, I ended up building a company to
Compete with upgrade directly. Yes.
Brilliant. That's amazing isn't it? So my
Brand deal is pending.
Thank you so much. Thank
you sir.  awesome man, this
Vaj fun.
like again a very long conversation that
we usually have but this time it was longer
then usual because our calls are usually painful in
The Nice.  Yes. We still
talked for an hour and a half
Let's take it.
Meaning, let's talk. nothing
Some of it
remains unfiltered.  Hi
What's up big man?
How deep have you gone, brother?
It’s a good thing isn’t it
Brother.
It's
good.
Brother.
It's
good.
Brother.
It's
good.
What a cool setup man.
Gorham.
Good you like it.  This
man is very good. Good
where are you playing the
table test?  Here it is.
He will not be able to
play.  oh no remove it a little
We could have played
here.  When I had to
play for the first time
We could have played
here.  When I had to
play for the first time
We could have played
here.  When I had to
play for the first time
Used to play at home.  Yes.
same thing happened at home earlier
We used to do it after removing the sofa and then playing.
Are you in Mumbai?  Where
are you keeping it? right here
You are keeping it,
right? This is
fine right?  Yes.  you
You are keeping it,
right? This is
fine right?  Yes.  you
You are keeping it,
right? This is
fine right?  Yes.  you
what do you
drink?  Good.
This is your new
addiction.  I like it.
It feels great to me Makes me feel better than anyone else
less guilty about myself you become a bodybuilder
He is trying to make his body beyond limits
What do new explorations say?
it's great keep it up me too I also do
a lot of workout thank you so much this episode
Now you need three things to see you through till the end
First of all you have to subscribe this channel
Do it because the more you subscribe the more
We will bring equally good and valuable guests
You will find number two for me in the comments
Tell me what you liked about this episode
And what else did we find dirty so that we can forget those mistakes
Could not repeat it. and which such guest?
are you want to see back our
on the podcast so we can bring them in and
To be able to give you maximum value. End
Number three, this episode is about one person
Please share because one conversation
Can change someone's life. I will see you
Next time. Until then keep figuring up.
[music]